<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>reazzon on Reazzon</title>
    <link>/categories/reazzon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in reazzon on Reazzon</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 10:01:15 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/reazzon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>30 days yoga challenge to find my inner balance</title>
      <link>/posts/yoga-challenge/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 10:01:15 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/yoga-challenge/</guid>
      <description>I am not a calm person, or someone who finds equilibrium very easily. I tend to go to extremes in everything I do, either giving too much or too little. For me, consistency in what I do is the most difficult thing to achieve.
I have always been jealous of my mother, who is a calm and self-controlled person. Nothing is important enough to disturb her inner peace, or lose sleep over it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From being a mentor to being a mentee</title>
      <link>/posts/ralucamentor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 10:01:15 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/ralucamentor/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On a journey to find my balance</title>
      <link>/posts/findmybalance/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 10:01:15 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/findmybalance/</guid>
      <description>In the last couple of weeks I have constantly had that feeling of frustrastion coming from doing what I need vs doing what I want. I enjoy the fulfilment of completing the most important task for that day, or reaching the end of a project, or simply just cutting a task off my To Do list. But I equally enjoy (maybe even more) the happiness of doing something for myself, for my soul.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Reazzon: Inclusive workplace</title>
      <link>/posts/diversity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 10:01:15 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/diversity/</guid>
      <description>Diversity and inclusion are now amongst the values of all modern businesses, but what does it actually mean to have a diverse work force and make sure everybody feels like they belong? How is the journey like for “the minorities” and can businesses do more to support them?
My journey in the corporate world has been scattered with a lot of frustration along the way. I was born and raised in Eastern Europe, where success is defined by a black and white approach: you&amp;rsquo;re either right, and you&amp;rsquo;re successful, or you&amp;rsquo;re wrong, and you&amp;rsquo;re failing at whatever you are trying to achieve.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>